(Sheldon:)She gave it to my sister
about her boyfriend,
(Sheldon:)my brother about his girlfriend,
(Sheldon:)my father about his girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)That one had some
un-Christian words in it.
(Amy:)Well, she likes me.
(Amy:)You know, there's a chance
she might be okay with it.
(Sheldon:)Eh, I don't know.
(Sheldon:)I am her precious little boy.
And you did take my flower.
(Penny:)Do boys have flowers?
(Leonard:)Who knows what he has
down there.
(Sheldon:)Mm.
(Sheldon:)Anyway...
(Mary:)Thank you, God, for the food
we are about to receive
(Mary:)and for the nourishment
of our bodies
(Mary:)and bless the hands
that prepared it.
(Mary:)Amen.
(Sheldon:)Given that your
hands prepared it,
(Sheldon:)isn't that a little
self-serving?
(Mary:)You start changing
the words to the prayers,
(Mary:)next thing you know, you're
in a church with a guitar.
(Amy:)Thank you for cooking,
it looks delicious.